oooms.org 2017-03-31

# Privacy - OOOMS.ORG

### Privacy Policy:

**This statement relates to the privacy practices of** _[ **www.oooms.org**](http://www.oooms.org/)_ **in connection with our website.**

**General statement**

_[**www.oooms.org**](http://www.oooms.org/)_ **respects your right to privacy and actively seeks to maintain the privacy rights of those who share**

**personal information with www.oooms.org**

**Gathering and use of personal information**

_[**www.oooms.org**](http://www.oooms.org/)_ **does not collect any personal information about you on their website other than information which you**

**voluntarily provide.** _[ **www.oooms.org**](http://www.oooms.org/)_ **only makes use of such information in line with the purpose for which you provided it**

**as is necessary to provide you with the information and/or service you require. www.oooms.org will not disclose your**

**information to any third party without informing you first or unless it is required to use a third party to process the**

**information for us. Should we need a third party to process information www.oooms.org requires these third parties to**

**comply with their instructions and also require that the third party agree not to use your personal information for**

**their own purposes unless you have explicitly consented for them to do so.**

**Use of cookies**

**Our website uses cookies which are small text files placed on your computer by our website so that www.oooms.org’s**

**website scripts are able to analyze how visitors use our website and record visitor preferences. www.oooms.org’s website**

**uses two different types of cookies:**

 **www.oooms.org uses cookies to collect traffic data to the website to help us analyze how visitors use the**

**site. Such cookies are used to collect anonymous data on user behavior and are not used to**

**identify a user personally. The information stored in the cookie is used to evaluate use of this**

**website and to compile statistical reports on website activity for www.oooms.org.**

 **On your first visit to this website you will see a message informing you about cookies. Clicking**

**the “hide this message” button causes the website script to set a cookie which records your**

**preference improving your experience on our website**

**Disabling cookies**

**Cookies may be blocked by adjusting the browser settings on your device. Blocking cookies will cause no loss of**

**functionality.**

**Links**

_[**www.oooms.org**](http://www.oooms.org/)_ **is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other websites. The privacy practices on these**

**websites may differ from that on the www.oooms.org’s website, and it is advised that you review the other websites’**

**policies before providing personal information.**

**Right of Access**

**You have the right to ask for a copy of your personal data. Should you want to take advantage of this right email**

**us at oooms.org@gmail.com To protect your privacy, you may be asked to provide suitable proof of identification. If any**

**of your details are incorrect please let us know and we will correct them.**

**Revisions to Privacy Policy**

**www.oooms.org may revise this privacy statement from time to time. Changes to this privacy policy will be posted here so**

**you should check this page periodically to review the most recent statement.**
